{
    "subject": "resource/WUPA",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCountry",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "WUPA is located in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9675277471542358,
            "question": "Is WUPA within the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.898890495300293,
            "question": "Where is WUPA located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322694659233093,
            "question": "What kind of place is WUPA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7317968606948853,
            "question": "In what country is WUPA situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5474188327789307,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks near WUPA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3178960680961609,
            "question": "Is WUPA a good place to live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2784513235092163,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about WUPA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2706685960292816,
            "question": "What are some popular activities in WUPA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2074342966079712,
            "question": "What is the climate like in WUPA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14846163988113403,
            "question": "Does WUPA have a strong cultural scene?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WUPA is located in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_150_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in WUPA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_150_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular activities in WUPA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_150_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about WUPA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_150_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_150_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that WUPA is a television station licensed to Atlanta, Georgia, United States. Therefore, the statement \"WUPA is located in the United States\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}